The culprit who shot Chieri's father has not been found yet.
If the DGTO is behind this, the truth will remain shrouded in darkness forever.
That's horrible!
With Chieri in her condition, we will face difficulties with our plan to take back Akibastar.
She must recover no matter what.
Please don't phrase it like that!
Kanata!
I can't imagine how painful it must have been.
Her dad was murdered right in front of her!
Big Sis...
It's gonna be rough. Getting over a parent's death isn't something you do overnight.
She'll have to!
If we are defeated and entertainment is lost, the DGTO's control over the galaxy will be absolute!
AKB0048 is the last glimmer of hope we have.
Tsubasa's right. We have to do this or the next generation of children will grow up in darkness!
She's right. If all of us don't shine as bright as a center nova, we might as well call it quits.
Takamina-san.
We'll cause a reaction with the dualium and make the Kirara shine like the sun!
Sayaka-san.
Big Sis!
Alright, let's get to shining!
Mm!
めRIOT grim
Let's get married!
Anyways, break off mic
Let's go!
Cool to the show!
We're gonna be, um, you know
Fl spacesa
Let's play like this
Let'm to do the best now
A eternal forest
Fly to Philadelphia
I have to break my ownful teeth
If you're in the corner
I'll see you next time.
Sorry about the disgusting disguise.
Let's change it back, shall we?
They really wrecked this place, huh?
Watching Zero Zero perform on the main stage at Akibastar was my lifelong dream.
Guess it's gone now.
I don't understand.
Why is the sky this color?
They've chosen a color that will keep everyone's spirits down.
That way they won't be misled by entertainment.
Those jerks.
No wonder everyone's eyes are so lifeless.
We'll free you all.
Don't worry.
The water has infiltrated.
We can't find them here.
Don't you think it would be lovely if it were pink?
I certainly do.
A pink sky would be the greatest thing ever.
Don't move!
So, that's a ration and a foot massage you owe me.
Thank you very much, Megu-chan.
And the 76th generation as well!
Home sweet home!
What is this?
Chef Papa, we've got quite a haul.
Ready to cook?
Yep.
Lay it on me.
Can we eat this?
That's fine.
It's full of vitamins.
It even has medicinal uses.
How about this?
Is it good?
Let me worry about that.
Hooray!
You said we can eat it, Megu-chan!
Let's go get some more!
We're witnessing the birth of a new breed of idols!
The Wino!
Leader!
Keep it together!
Tomo-chin, how are you feeling?
Fine.
Thank you, Koji-haru.
Tomo-chin-san!
Are you hurt?
No.
I just have a bad headache is all.
Sorry you have to see us in such a pathetic state.
I'll call a doctor for you.
You should be getting proper medical attention.
The people of Akipasta hate us.
I doubt they'd help out now.
What?
It's true.
They think we abandoned them when the DES attacked.
No way.
We had no choice but to retreat.
With Yuko-kun, it was the only thing we could do.
But the city was seized immediately afterwards, and the DGTO's propaganda began.
They brainwashed them in such a short amount of time?
If they're suppressing the net and media using the color of the sky...
By the way, what is this place?
For Zero-Zero, this is a sacred space.
It's a holy ground that even members are normally not allowed to enter.
Since we got here, I feel as though I can hear something.
Like someone's voice is echoing inside me.
A voice?
Tomo-chin, your Kirara.
Damn it!
Stop caring about the way you look already!
Your Kiraras aren't even twinkling yet!
You'll never cause a reaction with a dualium like this!
Wrong!
Tsubasa, calm down.
You can do better than this!
Stronger! Faster!
Use your whole body down to your fingertips!
Like this!
Do it like this!
Tsubasa, what are you...
Tsubasa-san?
Come on, try it!
Like this!
I think she feels she can't rely on the members.
Must be maddening, poor thing.
I agree.
But in her current condition...
You're kidding!
The Kiraras!
Tsubasa-san!
I can't do it.
Not anymore.
Nagisa,
you're the only one who can do it.
All of you,
Akibastar is counting on you.
Tsubasa's actually crying.
Yeah.
All right, ladies!
You all saw how Tsubasa made the Kirara shine.
She graduated from Zero-Zero a long time ago,
but she could still make those babies glow!
Do you want to know why?
It's her strong feelings.
Her passion drives her.
A strong feeling?
What are we going to do if the current members can't do it?
Look at how much this old hag Tsubasa can do.
Old hag?
What do you say, everyone?
You're gonna let this old bat beat you?
You too, Michonne?
Okay, let's continue with our lesson.
Right!
It looks like your passion and drive has ignited everyone else's.
Chan Tsubasa, good job!
They needed to believe in themselves,
and I needed to trust in them.
A strong feeling.
We'll do it!
We'll take back Akibastar!
Akibastar, our home.
Our special place.
A place that accepted us.
A place that took our dreams and made them possible.
Where we'll fulfill...
Our promise.
ковry Jack
, at theş
Jesus in that peace.
Theş
Every one of us.
In our own place.
Each one carrying her own thoughts.
We share the same dream.
One dream.
We want to become part of 0048.
Pushed forward by our dream.
We embarked...
On the train of dreams that would lead us to Akibastar!
What?
Are we on a train?
I could have sworn we were on the flying get having a lesson a moment ago.
Beautiful.
Hey, what's going on here?
It's stopping.
But where has it taken us?
Takamina-san.
It's opening.
This looks like...
It's Akibastar!
Are you alright, Takamina?
We saw it.
What?
We saw it!
The place of our dreams, where our hopes came to life!
We saw Akibastar!
Does this mean the Kiraras caused the dualium to react like we hoped?
It must be!
With this much?
We may be able to do it!
Good work, everyone!
Face it, we're that good!
Subasa-san!
Huh?
It's Nagisa!
She still hasn't woken up!
Oh no!
Nagisa?
Nagisa!
Where did everyone go?
Nagisa.
Chiyeri!
Where...
Where are we?
I don't know.
Chiyeri, how did you get here?
I just...
I remember being in the darkness.
I felt like I would be crushed by the darkness if I stood still.
So I danced.
I thought I'd be able to forget everything while I did.
Nagisa?
I think I've seen this before.
What?
Hey, is there someone over there?
No way.
You're right.
Yuko-san?
Let's get off!
Yeah!
Yuko-san!
I can't go any farther.
This is the end.
That's...
The 13th generation Ahchan!
And the 6th generation Yuihan!
And all the other Centernovas!
But...
But why?
Look at them.
They're shining!
Yeah.
But...
But why?
Look at them.
They're shining!
Yeah...
But...
What is that place?
A stage?
I can see Ahchan!
I can see her, but I can't reach her!
Yuko-san...
Nagisa!
You're alright!
Thank goodness!
Are you alright?
Yuko-sanas?
Yuko?
What are you talking about?
Jamie!
Nagisa!
Did you?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I don't think we were dreaming.
I see.
You must have seen the AKB48 theater.
Before Earth was destroyed,
AKB48 started on a small stage in a town called Akihabara in Japan.
The girls who gathered there took the first steps of what would become your dream.
But Earth's been gone for a long time.
That's true.
But the stage isn't actually on the planet.
It's probably a space where strong feelings have gathered.
Yeah.
Okay.
Then why hasn't Yuko been able to reach it yet?
Well, if I had to guess, she probably hasn't fully become a center nova yet.
No way!
Yuko-san had the shine of a center nova on AKB48!
You're right.
The conditions for the birth of a center nova were met.
But in Yuko's case, she didn't meet the conditions for the full-on disappearance.
I don't understand. What was she missing?
The most important condition. Surpass time and space. Become one with everything.
Surpass time and space?
Yes. The members, the audience, the staff, and the venue aren't enough.
The future and the past. Cease to be separate. I can't express it with words.
You become one with everything. Existing everywhere and nowhere.
In almost a terrifying trance-like state. That's how a center nova disappears.
But the way Yuko disappeared, it looked to me as though she appeared to escape into loneliness.
Then there's no time to waste. Let's go! To Akibastar!
Right!
The concert is this way. Please form a line and wait.
Is this the right place?
Yeah. I got word from Tsubasa-san a while ago.
She said they'd bring the flying get in around this area.
But how will they manage that?
Akibastar is currently surrounded by the DES. They'll never get through.
Let's believe in Zero-Zero and wait.
Alright. It's time to take back Akibastar.
Hyperspace jump standby!
Dualium synchronizer operating normally. There are no problems with the Kiara drive either.
Even if the jump succeeds, we don't know where we'll end up.
Take the wheel, Mishan.
Sure! I'll drive! Leave everything to me!
Kojiharu! Toma-chen! Move to the stage and meet us at the concert!
Okay!
Tsubasa-san!
What's wrong?
I have a message for you from Sensei-sensei.
Toma-chen! Are you saying you can hear it?
Yes, but I didn't hear words. I felt it resonate directly inside my body.
The key to our plan to take back Akibastar is, as Sensei-sensei put it, no name.
No name, huh? A nameless entity?
I don't know the details.
I see. There's no time to think on it now. Go. Prepare for the concert.
Yes.
Listen closely, everyone. The concert will start upon arrival.
The DGTO-Occupy Akibastar will certainly request reinforcements from the DES.
Until then, we'll make the concert as exciting as possible.
Tieri, I'm sorry.
I feel bad. When we were on Lancaster, you saved me when I lost my voice during the concert.
But I can't do anything for you.
There's a door that would never open for me.
I thought everything I wanted was inside.
But it would never open for me.
It was because I stayed in the darkness.
So one day I decided to go into the light.
And here I am.
Tieri.
I know what's going to happen.
I will become the Center Nova and go beyond that door this time.
Huh?
So I'll do it. To take back Akibastar.
Yeah. Let's all open that door. Together.
I'm sure you'll be able to reach your father.
The residents have been relocated. We're going to stop the DES here if it comes to that.
Hey, look up there!
Huh? A gate!
Could it be Zero-Zero?
Watch out!
We're going to class!
Mi-chan, this is gonna be rough!
We're being visited by the goddesses of theater!
A-K-B!
Zero-Zero-48!
We're back, everyone!
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, oh...
We're back, everyone!
All right, all right!
On the surface of our bodies,
Our bodies, both and women,
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh, oh...
How dare they do it now?
They have to move!
How bad?
Trader!
Go ho!
But why?
Why are they doing this?
The people of Aki Buster used to be so kind!
You're kidding!
What's going on?
If we don't hurry, the DES will invade!
Don't be afraid!
Trust yourselves and act as one!
This is what your training was for!
How are we supposed to make our hearts run now?
It's impossible!
You're kidding!
Aki Buster turned on them!
Go ho!
We'll have to use the concert to heighten their emotions!
We have to reach their hearts!
Connect with them!
If the Keradas and Dualium react to that collective subconsciousness, then...
In order to do that, the audience's feelings are important as well!
This is really bad!
I don't think the Dualium will react in response to the members alone!
What did you say?
Go ho!
Go!
Buster used to be so nice and filled with happiness, but now they're all this terrifying.
It's okay. I'm sure you'll be all right.
The D.E.S. I won't let it.
Nagisa. I won't let it end like this. I'll make it all right.
I won't let it end like this. I won't let it end like this.
Two人が出会った頃 夢などまだ鐘だった
それくらい時が過ぎ 花は咲くのだろう
この涙を君に捧ぐ もっと君が輝くな
ずっと見守ってた 深奥の空から
今僕は雨になろう
Ah 君に捧ぐ こんな僕にできることは
君の虚しさを 少しでも癒すこと
さあ 僕は雨になろう
救急の後
アクセスルの削り